fortniteintel.com 2019-05-07

# Privacy Policy | Fortnite INTEL

The following terms govern the use of Dexerto Limited websites and technologies, along with other online features and services, including but not limited to emails, forums, giveaways, newsletters (collectively, the “ **Platforms** ”) operated by Dexerto Limited and our subsidiaries (collectively “ **Dexerto** ” “ **we** ”  **us** ”  **or** “ **our** ”).

Dexerto reserves the right to modify these terms at any time, without warning, with the new terms coming into immediate effect from the moment they are published. It is advised that you take the time to periodically check for updates across our platforms.

We are committed to safeguarding the privacy of our Platform visitors and users. This policy applies where Dexerto acts as a data controller, with respect to the personal data of our Platform visitors and users, i.e. where we determine the purposes and means of the processing of that personal data.

You can control what cookies you consent to us using, in accordance with our cookies policy.

 **Information We Collect**

There are several categories of data that we may collect and process during your time using our Platforms.

  *   **Personal Data**

This is data that identifies you, or enables us to contact you, and may include but not be limited to your name, address, sex, email address, date of birth/age, occupation, location, salary range, language preference, or photo if you’ve provided one. Most of this data is only collected if you provide it voluntarily.

  *   **Non-Personal Data**

This is data used for statistical and analytical purposes, combined with other users of the website. This kind of data allows us to improve our Platforms, and learn important information about how users act when they visit our Platforms. Information in this category includes but is not limited to device type, browser type, location, and other anonymous data.

 **How We Use Your Information**

  *       **During the Provision of Platforms**

Your information may be used in the daily running of our Platforms, including giveaways and comments sections.

  *       **During the Improvement of Platforms**

Your information may be used to improve our Platforms, provide you with personalised content, interact with you, notify you of changes, and identify any issues.

  *       **Communication**

Where you’ve consented, we may use your information to contact you, in compliance with applicable law. Your prior, opt-in consent will be required for this communication.

  *       **Advertising**

Your information may be used to deliver adverts to you that we believe that you’ll be interested in. These adverts might be delivered by a third-party, or directly by Dexerto. The type of advertisements that you see will be in-part decided by your cookie consent.

  *       **Engagement**

Your information may be used to monitor how both you and other users engage with our Platforms as a whole, allowing us to deliver the best content and tailor our website to improve your experience.

  *       **Security**

Your information may be used for security purposes, to allow us to identify and remedy an incident of this nature.

  *       **Legal**

In rare cases, your information may be used, either in defending legal rights of Dexerto or our users, or subject to applicable law, in response to court of governmental orders. If we believe you have violated our Terms and Conditions or other published guidelines, or there are grounds to suggest you are engaging in any illegal activity, we may be forced to release your information.

 **How We Work with Third Parties**

Dexerto may, in some instances, disclose personal information to third-parties when it is appropriate, in order to deliver a service or product, or to help us improve your experience with us, or when required by law.

As part of our dedication to securing your personal information, we have in place contracts with third parties to ensure your information remains secure and is limited to necessary use only.

We will never pass on your information, without your express written consent, unless obligated. There may be circumstances where your information is passed over for legal reasons, to regulatory authorities upon request, law enforcement, courts, or other bodies of a similar nature.

If you enter our competitions, it may also be necessary to pass over information in-order for Dexerto to fulfil the prize.

 **Retaining and Storing Your Information**

Any information we store on you, we hold securely and for as long as we need to in order to provide our services and products in accordance with applicable law.

We take every step feasible to ensure that your user information is retained and processed for the minimum necessary period.

If you opt out of any of our services, we will retain the minimum necessary amount of data to enable you to keep using our Platforms.

 **Individuals Under 13**

Our Platforms are not intended for use by children under the age of 13. No one under the age of 13 should be accessing our Platforms or providing us with any information. If someone under the age of 13 does disclose information about themselves in a public area, consequences may occur that are not intended for someone of their age. Should it be highlighted to us that we are storing data on any children under the age of 13, that data will be removed from our system as soon as physically possible. By using our Platforms, you warrant you are over the age of 13.

 **External Links  **

This Privacy Policy applies exclusively to Dexerto and our Platforms. Our website may contain links to external websites. Dexerto is in no way responsible for the content or privacy policies of these websites. We recommend that you take the time to read the privacy policies of other websites that you visit. Similarly, if you are redirected to Dexerto from a third-party, their privacy policy or practices will not apply to our Platforms.

 **Cookies**

A cookie is a file that is stored on your browsing device, used to communicate with the websites that you visit about various preferences of your user experience.

For more information about cookies and our cookie policy, please [click here.](https://fortniteintel.com/cookies-policy/)

 **Contact Us**

If you have any questions about our policy, or your personal information, you can contact us by post at the following address:

Dexerto Limited

Attn: Data Privacy Manager

15, Queens Square

Leeds

LS2 8AJ

United Kingdom

Alternatively, you can use this email address: [Privacy@dexerto.com](mailto:Privacy@dexerto.com)
